Evil is closer than you think.
The Clovehitch Killer is a drama, mystery, crime film directed by Duncan Skiles.
A picture-perfect family is torn apart after Tyler finds a cache
of disturbing images in his father's possession.
He begins to suspect that the man he trusts most in the world may be
responsible for the murder of 13 women ten years prior.
Don, played by Dylan McDermott.
Tyler, played by Charlie Plummer.
Cindy, played by Samantha Mathis.
Kassi, played by Madisen Beaty.
Susie, played by Brenna Sherman.
Billy, played by Lance Chantiles-Wertz.
The Clovehitch Killer is a 2018 American coming-of-age thriller film, directed by
Duncan Skiles in his directorial debut and written by Christopher Ford.
It stars Dylan McDermott, Charlie Plummer, Samantha Mathis, and Madisen Beaty.
The film was mostly inspired by the story of real life serial
killer Dennis Rader, also known as the BTK Killer.
It premiered at LA Film Festival, on September 22, 2018, and it received a limited
theatrical release, on November 16, 2018, distributed by IFC Midnight.
The film explores themes of investigation, coming of age,
serial killer, psychological thriller, church.
The tone is dark and emotional and mind_bending.